Guide to the Douglas Menuez Photography Collection MSS.PHOTO.0451
Dept. of Special Collections & University Archives
- Series 7. Accession 2008-179, 52.0 Linear feet
  - Subseries 1. Jobs
    - Kaplan, Jerry (Author "Start Up") (2 of 2), 1995 April (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Kare, Susan (Flat-box 41, Folder 13)
      b/w negatives: roll: 26788 (no corresponding contact sheet)
    - Katzen, Mollie, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 4)
      37 color transparencies
    - Katzen, Mollie, 1984 (Flat-box 41, Folder 14)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 12028-12030
    - Kids with Computers, 1984 (Box 26, Folder 5)
      35 color transparencies
    - Komisar, Milton (sculptor) (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Kraus, Bill (3COM), 1985-1989 (Box 26, Folder 7)
      115 color transparencies
    - Kurtzig, Sandra (ASK Computers), 1988 May (Box 26, Folder 8)
      39 color transparencies, 2 color prints
    - Kurtzig, Sandra (ASK Computers), 1988 May (Flat-box 41, Folder 15)
      color negatives (2)
    - LAM, 1989 January (Box 26, Folder 9)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 10256-10259, 12526-12531 (negatives available except 10257)
    - LAM, 1989 January (Flat-box 41, Flat-box 16)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 10256, 10258-10259, 12526-12531 (corresponding contact sheets available)
    - Lee, Robert E. (descendant of General Robert E. Lee), 1983 March (Box 26, Folder 10)
      color transparencies: rolls: 2312-2314, unnumbered
    - Levin, Jerry, 1987 February (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Limbach & Limbach (1 of 2), 1996 October (Box 26, Folder 12)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 01055-01068 (corresponding negatives available)
    - Limbach & Limbach (1 of 2), 1996 October (Flat-box 41, Folder 17)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 01055-01068 (corresponding contact sheets available)
    - Limbach & Limbach (2 of 2), 1996 October (Box 26, Folder 13)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 01069-01082, 08713-08714 (corresponding negatives available)
    - Limbach & Limbach (2 of 2), 1996 October (Flat-box 41, Folder 18)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 01069-01082, 08713-08714 (corresponding contact sheets available)
    - Lorp, Dana (Toyota), 1996 April (Box 26, Folder 14)
      12 b/w prints; b/w contact sheets: rolls: C1-C13 (corresponding negatives available)
    - Lorp, Dana (Toyota), 1996 April (Flat-box 41, Folder 19)
      b/w negatives: rolls: C1-C3 (corresponding contact sheets available)
    - LSI Logic, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 15)
      21 color transparencies
    - Macintosh Factory (Box 27, Folder 1)
      4 color transparencies
    - Medical Ethics, 1988 (Box 27, Folder 2)
      71 color transparencies
    - Microsoft "Small Bus" contact extras (Flat-box 104, Folder 4)
    - Mok, Clement, 1989 (Box 27, Folder 3)
      22 color transparencies
    - NEC (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 27, Folder 4)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 71657-71671 (corresponding negatives available)
    - NEC (1 of 2), 1995 (Flat-box 42, Folder 1)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 71657-71671 (corresponding contact sheets available)
    - NEC (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 27, Folder 5)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 71672-71674, 71798-71805 (corresponding negatives available)
    - NEC (2 of 2), 1995 (Flat-box 42, Folder 2)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 71672-71674, 71798-71805 (corresponding contact sheets available)
    - NEC (1 of 4), 1996 January (Box 27, Folder 6)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 10861-10868 (corresponding negatives available)
    - NEC (1 of 4), 1996 January (Flat-box 42, Folder 3)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 10861-10868 (corresponding contact sheets available)
    - NEC (2 of 4), 1996 January (Box 27, Folder 7)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 10869-10878 (corresponding negatives available for 10870, 10872-10875, 10878)
    - NEC (2 of 4), 1996 January (Flat-box 42, Folder 4)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 10870, 10872-10875, 10878 (corresponding contact sheets available)
    - NEC (3 of 4), 1996 January (Box 27, Folder 8)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 10879-10881, 11585-11589 (corresponding negatives available)
    - NEC (3 of 4), 1996 January (Flat-box 42, Folder 5)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 10879-10881, 11585-11589 (corresponding contact sheets available)
    - NEC (4 of 4), 1996 January (Box 27, Folder 9)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 11590-11595 (corresponding negatives available)
    - NEC (4 of 4), 1996 January (Flat-box 42, Folder 6)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 11590-11595 (corresponding contact sheets available)
    - Nelder, Wendy, 1986 November (Flat-box 42, Folder 7)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 81610-81613
    - Nerli, Maureen (Agent Orange, Women in Vietnam) (Box 27, Folder 10)
      color transparencies: rolls: 21378-21380
    - Newton (Apple Computers, Nara Japan), 1993 (Box 27, Folder 11)
      color contact sheets: 4 unnumbered rolls
    - Newton (Apple Computers, Nara Japan), 1993 (Flat-box 42, Folder 8)
      color negatives: 4 unnumbered rolls
    - Newton, 1992 July - August (Box 27, Folder 12)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 81321-81328, 10-17, 40-45, 60004 (no corresponding negatives)
    - Newton, 1993 June (Box 27, Folder 13)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 80699-80707, 80437-80440, 80442-80451, 80528-80541, 82332-82337 (no corresponding negatives)
    - Newton, 1993 June - July (Box 27, Folder 14)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 82338-82374, 81178-81181 (no corrensponding negatives)
    - Newton CES (1 of 3), 1992 May (Box 27, Folder 15)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 79119-79130 (no corresponding negatives)
    - Newton CES (2 of 3), 1992 May (Box 27, Folder 16)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 79131-79142, 80170, 79159, 79160 (no corresponding negatives)
    - Newton CES (3 of 3), 1992 May (Box 27, Folder 17)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 79143-79159 (no corresponding negatives)
    - Newton - Paris (1 of 3), 1992 (Box 28, Folder 1)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 8265, 8273-8281, 8286-8300 (no corresponding negatives)
    - Newton - Paris (2 of 3), 1992 (Box 28, Folder 2)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 8301-8309, 8358-8371, 8374-8379, 9000, 9003 (no corresponding negatives)
    - Newton - Paris (3 of 3), 1992 (Box 28, Folder 3)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 8380-8402, 8424-8426 (no corresponding negatives)
    - Newton, 1992 December (Box 28, Folder 4)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 82583-82591 (no corresponding negatives)
    - Newton (1 of 2), 1993 January (Box 28, Folder 5)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 63427-63430, 63432-63435, 63437-63440, 63442, 63444-63447, 63449-63458 (no corresponding negatives)
    - Newton (2 of 2), 1993 January (Box 28, Folder 6)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 63527-63542, 68809 (no corresponding negatives)
    - Newton, 1993 February (Box 28, Folder 7)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 69314-69238
    - Newton, 1993 March (Box 28, Folder 8)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 67076-67077, 66846-66852, 66973-66978 (no corresponding negatives)
    - Newton CBIT (1 of 2), 1993 March (Box 28, Folder 9)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 64276-64286, 64288-64300 (no corresponding negatives)
    - Newton CBIT (2 of 2), 1993 March (Box 28, Folder 10)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 64301-64320, 64436-64439 (no corresponding negatives)
    - Newton (1 of 2), 1993 April (Box 28, Folder 11)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 64495-64517 (no corresponding negatives)
    - Newton (2 of 2), 1993 April (Box 29, Folder 1)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 64797-64812, 65259-65260, 65679-65683 (no corresponding negatives)
    - Newton (1 of 2), 1993 May (Box 29, Folder 2)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 70136-70155, 70158-70162 (no corresponding negatives)
    - Newton (2 of 2), 1993 May (Box 29, Folder 3)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 70283-70293, 70620-70631, 70675, 70893-70897, 71106 (no corresponding negatives)
    - Newton, 1993 June (Box 29, Folder 4)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 71391, 71449-71459 (no corresponding negatives)
    - Newton, 1993 June (Flat-box 104, Folder 5)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 71986, 80441
    - Newton book project, 1992-1993 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - NFL Football - Raiders vs. Seahawks, 1984 January 8 (Box 29, Folder 6)
      color transparencies: rolls: 37637-37651
    - NFL Football - Raiders vs. Seahawks (locker room shots), 1984 January 8 (Box 29, Folder 8)
      color transparencies: rolls: 37628, 37629
    - NFL Football - Raiders vs. Seahawks, 1984 January 8 (Box 29, Folder 7)
      color transparencies: rolls: 639, 640, 644, 648
    - NFL Football - Raiders vs. Seahawks, 1984 January 8 (Flat-box 42, Folder 9)
      color negatives: rolls: 04955, 04958, 04949, 04950 (no corresponding contact sheets)
    - NFL Football - Eagles vs. 49'ers, 1983 September 3 (Box 29, Folder 9)
      color transparencies: rolls: 38088-38098
    - NFL Football - Bears vs. 49'ers, 1985 October 19 (Box 29, Folder 10)
      color transparencies: rolls: 14936-14943, 700
    - NFL Football - Saints vs. 49'ers, 1985 September 29 (Box 29, Folder 11)
      color transparencies: rolls: 14157-14162
    - NFL Football - Bengals vs. 49'ers, 1984 November 4 (Box 29, Folder 12)
      color transparencies: rolls: 412-416, 418
    - NFL Football - Lions vs. 49'ers, 1984 January 1 (Box 30, Folder 1)
      color transparencies: rolls: 37195, 37202-37205, 194, 196-198, 207-210, 213
    - NFL Football - Broncos vs. 49'ers, 1985 August 19 (Box 30, Folder 2)
      color transparencies: rolls: 65933-65934, 63936-63938
    - NFL Football - Giants vs. 49'ers, 1984 December 29 (Box 30, Folder 3)
      color transparencies: rolls: 90342, 90344-90348, 90350-90353
    - NFL Football - Giants vs. 49'ers, 1979-1984 (Box 30, Folder 4)
      color transparencies: rolls: 90343, 90349
    - NFL Football - Seahawks vs. 49'ers, 1983 August 27 (Box 30, Folder 5)
      color transparencies: rolls: 19720-19727, 3 unnumbered
    - Nietshmann, Bernard (Audubon), 1992 (Box 30, Folder 6)
      color transparencies: 14 sheets
    - Nino's Seafood Palace (Salinas, CA), 1984 (Box 30, Folder 7)
      color transparencies: rolls: 17653-17655
    - Norman, David (CEO, Businessland Inc.), 1988 April (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Novak, Richard - Santa Cruz Skateboards, 1989 (Flat-box 42, Folder 10)
      color negatives: rolls: 12926-12928
    - NUMMI (New United Motor Manufacturing Inc.), 1984 (Box 30, Folder 9)
      color transparencies: rolls: 90056-90060
    - Odello, Bruna and Huerta, Kati - Pope's visit to San Francisco and Carmel, CA, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 10)
      color transparencies: rolls: 07538-07541, 07715-07719
    - Olivia Records (Flat-box 42, Folder 11)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 28371-28372
    - Online Biz Systems (Box 30, Folder 11)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 25535, 25447, 25449, 25450
    - Online Biz Systems (Flat-box 42, Folder 12)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 25535, 25447, 25449, 25450
    - Oshman, Ken (CEO, Rolm Corp.), 1984 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Oxford Power Plant, Modesto CA, 1988 (Box 30, Folder 13)
      color transparencies: 4 sheets
    - Packard, David (co-founder of Hewlett and Packard Co.), 1985 (Box 31, Folder 1)
      color transparencies: 1 sheet
    - Packard, David (co-founder of Hewlett and Packard Co.), 1985 (Flat-box 42, Folder 13)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 29627-29628
    - Packard, Julie (Monterey Bay Aquarium), 1984 (Box 31, Folder 2)
      color transparencies: roll: 29629
    - Pain inhibiting implant, UCSF Medical Center, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 3)
      b/w contact sheets: 5 sheets; 1 color print; 1 color transparency
    - Pain inhibiting implant, UCSF Medical Center, 1987 (Flat-box 42, Folder 14)
      color negatives: roll: 21829
    - Penhoet, Edward E. (CEO, Chiron), 1991 (Box 31, Folder 4)
      color transparencies
    - Perot, Ross (Box 31, Folder 5)
      6 b/w prints; 1 color transparency; 1 b/w transparency
    - Perot, Ross at the unveiling of Steve Jobs' "Next" Computer, 1988 October 12 (Flat-box 42, Folder 15)
      color negatives (1 strip)
    - Peters, Tom and Waterman, Bob - authors of In Search of Excellence, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 6)
      color transparencies; b/w contact sheets: rolls: 8421, 8423; 1 b/w print
    - Peters, Tom and Waterman, Bob - authors of In Search of Excellence, 1987 (Flat-box 42, Folder 16)
      b/w negatives: roll: 8421
    - PG&E Diablo Canyon, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - PIE Organization Announcement (Apple) (1 of 2) (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - PIE Organization Announcement (Apple) (2 of 2) (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Planet Out portraits, 1996 (Box 31, Folder 10)
      color transparencies; color contact sheets: rolls: 1-2, 6029-6039, 1 unnumbered (corresponding negatives available for all except unnumbered roll)
    - Planet Out portraits, 1996 (Flat-box 42, Folder 17)
      color negatives: rolls: 6029-6039, 2 unnumbered
    - Poker Championship - Las Vegas, 1985 (Box 31, Folder 11)
      color transparencies: rolls: 63548-63549
    - Stephens, Robertson, 1996 October (Box 31, Folder 12)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 07290, 00873-00880, 00885, 7289, 0888-0891; color contact sheets: rolls: 47078, 47092, 47092B, 47077, 47A, 47079-47088 (corresponding negatives available)
    - Rolm Corp., 1985 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - Romano - RMW Architects, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 2)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 8140-8165
    - Romano - RMW Architects, 1990 (Flat-box 43, Folder 1)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 8140-8165
    - Rowbotham (1 of 2), 1996 June (Box 32, Folder 3)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 02726-02740
    - Rowbotham (1 of 2), 1996 June (Flat-box 43, Folder 2)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 02726-02740
    - Rowbotham (2 of 2), 1996 June (Box 32, Folder 4)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 02741-02751
    - Rowbotham (2 of 2), 1996 June (Flat-box 43, Folder 3)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 02741-02751
    - Rulon-Miller, Virginia, 1988 February (Box 32, Folder 5)
      18 color transparencies
    - RX Media Portraits - Smolan, Naythons, Moffitt, 1990 (Box 32, Folder 6)
      color transparencies; b/w contact sheets: rolls: 8562-8564, 8289, 8331-8336
    - RX Media (Flat-box 43, Folder 4)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 23889-23890, 8562-8564, 8992, 8331, 8333, 2 unnumbered rolls
    - Sacramento Mayor, 1984 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Saffo, Paul - Institute for the Future, 1991 February (Flat-box 43, Folder 5)
      b/w negatives: roll: 9256
    - San Anselmo, 1983 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - Sanders, Jerry (President of Advanced Microcomputers), 1985 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Sanders, Jerry (President of Advanced Microcomputers), 1985 (Flat-box 43, Folder 6)
      b/w negatives: roll: 43-144
    - San Jose, CA - Bees, 1986 (Box 32, Folder 10)
      color transparencies: rolls: 99373-99379
    - San Jose, CA - Nightlife, 1987 (Box 32, Folder 11)
      color transparencies: 5 sheets
    - San Jose, CA - Reconstruction, 1985 (Box 32, Folder 12)
      color transparencies: 1 sheet; b/w contact sheets: 3 unnumbered rolls
    - San Jose, CA - Reconstruction (Flat-box 43, Folder 7)
      b/w negatives: 3 unnumbered rolls
    - Santa Clara University (Box 32, Folder 13)
      proof? (photocopy)
    - Sasso, John (Vice Chairman, Dukakis Campaign) (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - SAT Test Study, Kaplan (Berkeley, CA) (Box 32, Folder 15)
      color transparencies: rolls: 29917-29922, 82096-82099
    - Schoellhorn, Robert (CEO, Abbott Labs), 1989 (Box 32, Folder 16)
      color transparencies: 5 sleeves; loose
    - Schwab, Charles (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - Sheff, David, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 2)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 106123-106125
    - Sheff, David, 1990 (Flat-box 43, Folder 8)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 10621-10625
    - Shire, Willow (Digital Equipment Co.), 1993 (Box 33, Folder 3)
      color transparencies: 14 sleeves
    - Sierra Capital (Box 33, Folder 4)
      color transparencies: 18 sheets
    - Sierra Capital, 1989 (Box 33, Folder 5)
      color transparencies: 1 sleeve; b/w contact sheets: rolls: 13208-13210
    - Sierra Capital, 1989 (Flat-box 43, Folder 9)
      b/w negatives: roll: 13210
    - Sierra Ventures Annual Report, 1997 October (Box 33, Folder 6)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 1-14
    - Sierra Ventures Annual Report, 1997 October (Flat-box 43, Folder 10)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 1-14
    - Sierra Ventures (1 of 8), 1996 January (Box 33, Folder 7)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 10927-10940
    - Sierra Ventures (1 of 8), 1996 January (Flat-box 43, Folder 11)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 10927-10940
    - Sierra Ventures (2 of 8), 1996 January (Box 33, Folder 8)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 10941-10950, 11001-11003
    - Sierra Ventures (2 of 8), 1996 January (Flat-box 43, Folder 12)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 10941-10950, 11001-11003
    - Sierra Ventures (3 of 8), 1996 January (Box 33, Folder 9)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 11004-11014, 11016-11018
    - Sierra Ventures (3 of 8), 1996 January (Flat-box 43, Folder 13)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 11004-11014, 11016-11018
    - Sierra Ventures (4 of 8), 1996 January (Box 33, Folder 10)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 11019, 11050-11056, 11059-11064
    - Sierra Ventures (4 of 8), 1996 January (Flat-box 43, Folder 14)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 11019, 11050-11056, 11059-11064
    - Sierra Ventures (5 of 8), 1996 January (Box 34, Folder 1)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 11065-11080
    - Sierra Ventures (5 of 8), 1996 January (Flat-box 43, Folder 15)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 11065-11080
    - Sierra Ventures (6 of 8), 1996 January (Box 34, Folder 2)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 11081-11088, 11131-11133
    - Sierra Ventures (6 of 8), 1996 January (Flat-box 44, Folder 1)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 11081-11088, 11131-11133
    - Sierra Ventures (7 of 8), 1996 January (Box 34, Folder 3)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 11134-11145
    - Sierra Ventures (7 of 8), 1996 January (Flat-box 44, Folder 2)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 11134-11145
    - Sierra Ventures (8 of 8), 1996 January (Box 34, Folder 4)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 11146-11151, 11153-11164
    - Sierra Ventures (8 of 8), 1996 January (Flat-box 44, Folder 3)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 11146-11151, 11153-11164
    - Sierra Ventures, 1996 February (Box 34, Folder 5)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 12735, 12627-12631
    - Sierra Ventures, 1996 February (Flat-box 44, Folder 4)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 12735, 12627-12631
    - Sierra Ventures, 1997 September (Box 34, Folder 6)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 1-11
    - Sierra Ventures, 1997 September (Flat-box 44, Folder 5)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 1-11
    - Silicon Graphics, 1995 (Box 34, Folder 7)
      color transparencies: 6 sheets
    - Software Publishing, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 8)
      color transparencies; b/w contact sheets: rolls: 23481-23505
    - Software Publishing, 1989 (Flat-box 44, Folder 6)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 23481-23505, 24067, 24068, 24072
    - Software Publishing (1 of 2), 1989 May 23 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Software Publishing (2 of 2), 1989 May 23 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Solectron, 1994 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Sorenson, Keith (President/CEO, Raster Operations) (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Spears, Sheldon (AIDS), 1985 (Box 35, Folder 3)
      color transparencies: rolls: 97290-97293
    - Sports Medicine, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Spring Communications Corp., 1988 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Sprint Communications, 1985 (Box 35, Folder 6)
      color transparencies: 3 sheets
    - Sprint (Kansas City), 1996 November (Box 35, Folder 7)
      color contact sheets: rolls: 383-386, 20805-20808, 20832, 20839-20840
    - Sprint (Kansas City), 1996 November (Flat-box 44, Folder 7)
      color negatives: rolls: 383-386, 20805-20808, 20832, 20839-20840
    - Stanford Pub. Course, 1996 (Box 35, Folder 8)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 8618-8621, 8623-8645
    - Stanford Pub. Course, 1996 (Flat-box 44, Folder 8)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 8618, 8620, 8621, 8623-8626, 8628-8643, 8645
    - Stanford Students and Band, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 9)
      color transparencies: rolls: 83610-83612
    - Stanford Students and Band, 1984 (Flat-box 44, Folder 9)
      color negatives: roll: 82319
    - Stephens, Robertson, 1996 October (Flat-box 42, Folder 18)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 07290, 00873, 0880, 0885, 7289, 0888-0891; color negatives: rolls: 47078, 47092, 47077, 47A, 47079-47080
    - Stromberg, Arthur, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Thigpen, Peter (Levi's) (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Traffic Jam (Day in the Life of CA - San Francisco, Bay Area), 1988 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - Treybig, James C. (Tandem Computers), 1989 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - Tyson, Mike and Givens, Robin, Emmy Awards, 1988 (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Tyson, Mike and Bruno (boxing), 1989 February 5 (Flat-box 44, Folder 10)
      color negatives: roll: 11224
    - USFL Football, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 15)
      color transparencies: rolls: 4210-4216
    - USFL Football, 1983 (Flat-box 44, Folder 11)
      color negatives: rolls: 70434, 52-142, 52-143, 10064-10066
    - Waller Capital (Box 35, Folder 16)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 8240-8242
    - Waller Capital (Flat-box 44, Folder 12)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 8240-8242
    - Wells Fargo (Wall Street Big Traders), 1988 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Wells Fargo (1 of 6), 1994 January (Box 35, Folder 18)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 72249-72263
    - Wells Fargo (1 of 6), 1994 January (Flat-box 45, Folder 1)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 72249-72263
    - Wells Fargo (2 of 6), 1994 January (Box 35, Folder 19)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 72264-72279
    - Wells Fargo (2 of 6), 1994 January (Flat-box 45, Folder 2)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 72264-72279
    - Wells Fargo (3 of 6), 1994 January (Box 36, Folder 1)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 72280-72289, 72292-72294
    - Wells Fargo (3 of 6), 1994 January (Flat-box 45, Folder 3)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 72280-72289, 72292-72294
    - Wells Fargo Nikko (4 of 6), 1994 January (Box 36, Folder 2)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 72361-72374
    - Wells Fargo Nikko (4 of 6), 1994 January (Flat-box 45, Folder 4)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 72361-72374
    - Wells Fargo Nikko (5 of 6), 1994 January (Box 36, Folder 3)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 72375-72387
    - Wells Fargo Nikko (5 of 6), 1994 January (Flat-box 45, Folder 5)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 72375-72387
    - Wells Fargo Nikko (6 of 6), 1994 January (Box 36, Folder 4)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 72388-72394, 72496-72505
    - Wells Fargo Nikko (6 of 6), 1994 January (Flat-box 45, Folder 6)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 72388-72393, 72496-72505
    - Wells, George (LSI Logic), 1985 (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - Wendell, Peter - kids, 1997 September (Box 36, Folder 6)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 12-17 (corresponding negatives available)
    - Wendell, Peter - kids, 1997 September (Flat-box 45, Folder 7)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 12-17
    - Wild Family (recording artists), 1984 (Box 36, Folder 7)
      color transparencies: 11 sheets
    - Wilson Audio, 1989 (Box 36, Folder 8)
      color transparencies: roll: 15725
    - Wilson Audio, 1989 (Flat-box 45, Folder 8)
      color negatives: rolls: 15726-15727
    - Willens, Harold, 1985 (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - Wilson, Chas (brain surgeon, UCSF) (Box 36, Folder 10)
      2 b/w prints
    - Windmills - Altamont Pass, CA, 1986 (Box 36, Folder 11)
      color transparencies: 3 sheets; 3 b/w prints
    - Windows User (1 of 6), 1993 May (Box 36, Folder 12)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 71121-71126, 71107-71110
    - Windows User (1 of 6), 1993 May (Flat-box 45, Folder 9)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 71121-71126, 71107-71110
    - Windows User (2 of 6), 1993 May (Box 36, Folder 13)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 71111-71120
    - Windows User (2 of 6), 1993 May (Flat-box 45, Folder 10)
      b/w negatives: rolls: 71111-71120
    - Windows User (3 of 6), 1992 December - 1993 February (Box 36, Folder 14)
      b/w contact sheets: rolls: 62219-62224, 69197-69199
    - Windows User (3 of 6), 1992 December - 1993 February (Flat-box 45, Folder 11)